ebilling.com 2011-10-14

# Privacy Policy - DST Output

### Privacy Policy

We want you to understand our commitment to personal privacy and our use of information. DST Output respects your privacy and is committed to maintaining the privacy and confidentiality of personal data we collect. This Privacy Statement describes the ways we collect information from and about you, and what we do with the information, so that you may decide whether or not to provide information to us. DST Output reserves the right to make changes to this policy and to our related procedures at any time. As we make changes to our policy, we will update this Web page. 

“DST Output” includes DST Output LLC and its subsidiaries. 

#### WHAT DO WE COLLECT?

DST Output collects information from visitors who access the various parts of our Web site. We do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand, if you comment on a blog post, or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that law requires such disclosure.

In addition, our Web site automatically tracks and stores various log files, such as IP addresses and domain names for each visitor to the Web site, the last site visited before our Web site, aggregate information on what pages are accessed or visited and how often, and the kind of tools (monitor specs, browsers, etc) each visitor views our Web site with. These log files are delivered to third party service providers, who process the raw data and turn it into statistical reports for DST Output’s use.

We use “cookies” to enhance your visits to our website. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not store personal information about you, unless you knowingly provide it. Cookies can store non-personal information, such as what websites, pages, or advertisements your browser has accessed. We use cookies to track page counts and keep track of your navigation through our website. 

You do have control over cookies. Most browsers can be set to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. Most browsers can also be set to refuse to accept cookies, although this may affect your Internet experience. You can also erase cookies that are already on your computer. For more information about working with cookies, you should consult your user manual, FAQ, or “help” function of your specific browser and operating system software. 

We do not collect personal information about you as part of a web visit, but web visit information may be tied to other information (including personal information) we collect from you via chat, web forms, and the other means we describe in this Privacy Statement.

We preserve the content of your email, your email address, and our response so that we may better serve you. Depending on the content of your email, we may be required by existing laws and regulations to keep this information.

#### Links to Non-DST Output Web Sites

We may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. The privacy practices of those sites may differ from our practices and are not controlled by DST Output and not covered by this Privacy Statement. We do not make any representations about third-party websites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies before submitting your personal data.

#### WHAT DO WE USE THIS INFORMATION FOR?

We may use your information to provide access to secure areas of the Web site, recommend merchandise and services that might be of interest to you, to personalize your visit to our Web site, and to enable us to review develop and continually improve the information and resources we provide online. We also use this information to prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Web site and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

We use visitor information to send information about our company to visitors and to get in touch with them when necessary. We also use the information we collect to improve the content of our websites.

We use web visit information to measure interest in and develop our web pages and marketing plans, customize the content you view on your web visits based on your activity on past visits, and administer our Web site. 

We use cookies to help us recognize visitors as unique visitors (just a number) when they return to our Web site. We also use cookies to: allow us to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interest; avoid showing visitors the same advertisements repeatedly; compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our site and to help us improve the structure of our Web site (we cannot identify visitors personally in this way); count the number of anonymous users of our sites.

We use web beacons to count the number of times that our advertisements and web-based email content are viewed. We combine web beacon information with cookies to track activity on our website originating from advertisements and web-based email content.

We use information you provide to us via telephone calls, chat, email, web forms and other communications to correspond with you about services you may be interested in purchasing. Information you submit in writing, such as chat, email, and web form information is archived and may be tied to information that we collect about your web visits. 

#### SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

DST Output is committed to have in place security measures designed to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information in our possession. We use various security measures to protect the information we collect, as appropriate to the type of information, including encryption, firewalls, and access controls. We store information you provide to us on a computer system located in a controlled facility with a limited access. Our company databases are accessible only by DST Output employees, contractors and agents bound by a confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement with DST Output.

#### INQUIRIES OR COMPLAINTS

If you have a question or complaint about this Privacy Statement or our information collection practices, please contact us at [info@dstoutput.com](mailto:info@dstoutput.com). We will investigate the matter and are committed to resolve any privacy concerns that you may have.
